Made in ABC
Hey, Ryo. Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Really?
What about breakfast? Let's make it.
Yeah, thanks.
Okay.
Hey, it doesn't smell good, does it?
I'm really fine.
Please don't say that.
I'm not saying that.
Children are treasures in common.
What about club activities?
You can take a break, right?
Yeah, I'll go first.
What? You're kidding.
You should take a break at a time like this.
It's a practice match, so it's impossible.
Can't we do something about it?
At a time like this...
Good work, Ryo.
Thanks.
How was the practice match?
It was a complete defeat.
They were strong.
As expected of the best 8 last year.
How do you feel today? It's been a long time.
Oh, well...
I want to say that I want to go.
But I have to take a test today.
A final test.
Oh, really?
You have to get ready for it.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Good luck.
I want to go.
I want to go and relieve my stress.
I thought it was because of the stress that I couldn't organize it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Aren't you going to drink?
I'm going to drink.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Mom said it wasn't a big deal.
Are you still in a bad mood?
I'm fine.
But it's not like that.
What?
What's wrong?
Is it a promise?
What?
It's a promise?
I broke up with Seiya yesterday.
Oh, really?
I see.
That's what happens.
Actually,
You finally broke up with him.
I broke up with him.
But...
But what?
A baby has come.
What?
No way.
Really?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Go ahead.
It's a toast.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
I'm not sorry.
Thank you.
I'll be all alone for the rest of my life
I'll be all alone until I can smile
Feel so bad, don't run away
You can change anytime, baby
Feel so bad, take it out
Now is the time to try
What are you doing? Do it again
That kind of love is a lie
Feel so bad, don't run away
You can change anytime, baby
What are you doing? Do it again
That kind of love is a lie
Feel so bad, don't run away
You can change anytime, baby
Pop-ish music, Headphone
Today, I'll dig deeper into what I said last time.
Sorry.
Today wasn't the kanji test day.
Hey, don't say that.
Was it? Sorry, I forgot.
I'm going to go to the staff room and get the materials.
Please wait a minute. Sorry.
It's the same, right?
It's the same!
Is everyone ready?
Okay, I'll give you the answers.
Kawakami, please give me the answer to number one.
Please call me as soon as you get to the hotel.
Yes, that's correct.
If you want to be more natural, please call me as soon as you get to the hotel.
I'll call you as soon as I get to the hotel.
What's wrong?
No, it shouldn't be like that.
It's a summer vacation.
Summer vacation...
It's a hell for the teachers.
Everyone sees that, but is a summer vacation such a hell?
It shouldn't be a hell.
I teach my rights.
Are you going to take a break?
I'll take a break.
How much?
If you're going to take a break, just take a break.
What?
So how long?
About three weeks.
That's true.
There are a lot of things that you have to do as a school.
What do you think about that?
It's not something I have to do.
But someone has to do it.
That's why you don't change the flow of pushing yourself.
That's why there are no teachers.
It may be important to talk about ideals,
but there are things that you have to do in front of you.
If you ignore it without cooperation,
someone will suffer again.
That's why teachers should raise their voices.
There is no need to push yourself.
If we don't do what we do,
students will end up in an awkward situation.
Then the teacher should be in an awkward situation.
Why should I be in an awkward situation?
It can't be helped even if I meet an awkward person.
I didn't say that.
Then what do you mean?
Let's calm down for now.
Calm down.
No, I'm not calm.
After all,
if someone knows about it,
it will be all done by the management staff.
Do you understand?
That's what I think.
That's right.
I'll do it.
Right?
I'm envious of the hard work of G-sensei.
I wonder what the C class will do at the culture festival on the day of the break.
At this point,
I want to do this.
Sometimes I feel like this.
let's become one class
and do something we can do.
So hot, so disgusting.
Koukei, don't be so annoying with teachers.
You are obviously annoying.
Wait,
think about it
Nothing?
I don't have any.
Do you have any?
Whatever it is, is ok.
Whatever? That's the worst.
Think about it seriously.
There are so many people here.
We can make a group.
We can make memories together.
How about Kawakami?
I don't care.
You don't care about anything?
I don't care about anything.
How about Manaka?
Not particularly.
I don't care about anything.
For example, do you want to do something like this?
How about a play?
A play?
That's a good idea!
No, no, no.
I don't want to do that.
Seriously, guys.
When I was in high school, the play was so much fun.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
Let's do it, guys.
No, no.
It's just what Mr. Kaito wants to do.
The play is lame and it's a pain in the ass.
It's so lame, really.
Shohei!
Don't be ridiculous.
Don't beat around the bush.
I told you to shut up.
Tomura, shut up!
What's wrong with you guys?
You guys are so annoying.
No, no, no.
What's wrong with you guys?
You guys are so annoying.
Why?
It doesn't make sense.
You guys don't care about anything, do you?
Then don't complain to the guy who gave you the idea.
I think your idea is right.
Because I...
No, no, no.
But the play is good, isn't it?
I thought it was a little good, too.
Then, as a good example, Shohei and Moeko.
You guys play the role of the person in charge.
Koukei, you bastard.
What?
You don't like it?
I'll do it.
Let's do our best, Shohei.
But seriously, don't complain to the guy who gave you the idea.
What?
Yes, yes, yes.
Then, teacher.
The play is good, isn't it?
Rio teacher?
What's up?
You didn't hear it.
Rio, were you listening?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was thinking about something.
Rio, you don't care about the festival, do you?
Oh, no, no.
It's not like that.
Oh, well...
Then, the play is decided.
Yay!
Oh, the play.
What do you guys do in this situation?
teacher Ryo
Yes.
Sorry to bothering you before.
What?
Ms. Gou hasn't come home yet.
That's strange.
Do you know?
There's a rumor that Ms. Gou is in love with a student.
What?
It's just a rumor.
But Ms. Gou seems to be a little crazy.
That's right.
What's wrong with Ms. Ryo?
Doesn't she seem a little down?
Really?
That's not true.
Is that so?
I understand.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
I'm home.
You're early today.
Rio seems to be having a hard time.
Well, well, well.
Excuse me.
What is it?
Rio first?
Dad first.
It's not a big deal.
What is it?
Have you ever been to a snack bar called Natsuko in Ichikawa?
I have.
I was surprised to see your name on it.
My classmate's mother is the mother of that snack bar.
We met once.
Dad, do you go there often?
Oh, no.
A couple of times.
That's a coincidence.
Right?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
What is it?
What is it, Dad?
No, no.
Could it be that student?
Lena?
What?
Why do you know her?
I mean, she might be working at a store.
She seems to know a lot.
I don't know.
No, no, no.
Tell me.
I feel like she's drinking alcohol.
I don't know because I haven't checked it.
Maybe.
I'm sure.
I totally forgot.
I saw her at Ginza.
What?
Why did you know about that store?
She's a staff at my dad's company.
His name is Yoshizawa.
He met Lena at Ginza's club.
Then he went to her family's snack shop.
He liked it.
She used to work at Ginza.
I think he quit.
He didn't go there anymore.
By the way,
who is Yoshizawa?
He's a member of the National Assembly.
I see.
She's in high school.
That's so creepy.
That's crazy.
I see.
Hey Rio.
Do you know
that her father quit school because of this?
That's right.
If she finds out,
she'll be in trouble.
I see.
Hey.
What did you talk about with Rio?
Nothing special.
Tell me.
It's okay.
It's nothing.
Okay.
Ms. Sawaiya.
I need to talk to you.
Is it about Shinra?
No.
I have something to tell you.
I don't have anything to tell you.
I'll talk to you if something happens.
I mean it.
So,
don't hold back.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
I can't hold back.
I really want to get rid of my hair,
but it costs 500,000 yen.
That's a lot.
I know.
When I talked to my parents,
they told me to get rid of my hair
as soon as possible.
You're so yanky.
That's right.
You're a geneticist,
so I can't let you go.
Hey.
If you're here,
why don't you come with me?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Well,
thank you.
It's okay.
We're like theater directors.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I have to decide
until next week.
After school,
we'll have a meeting at the cinema.
Is that right?
Will Shohei come?
No, I'm not sure.
What about you, Moeko?
I'm not sure.
But
I want to be in a band.
Right?
We have to get members together.
Right.
I'm going to be a bassist.
Really?
I wonder if I can do it.
Hey.
Hello.
How's your rock life going?
I'm going to be a bassist.
Do you know the word Yoshihashi Rhythm?
Do you know?
No, I don't know.
It's not a word.
It's a saying, right?
Don't say that.
In a band, rhythm instruments
I mean drum and bass
are the most important.
If you underestimate drums and bass,
you'll die.
You can't even talk about rock.
Don't underestimate rock.
I'm going to work.
My ears are tight.
We have to find a drummer.
We have to find a good drummer.
What?
Mr. Nishiwaki.
Miyasako.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Nishiwaki.
What?
Would you like to join a band?
A band?
Good night.
See you later.
Oh, no.
Ms. Sasaoka.
Why are you here?
Tell her I'm coming.
See you later.
I wonder
if Lena is here.
She's not here.
She's a high school student, you know!
I know.
I'm so busy.
Sorry.
See you later.
It's not the time to worry about others.
But teachers worry about students.
However, I am not a qualified teacher.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
What's wrong? Are you tired?
Yes, because of that old woman.
I'm going to work when I finish high school.
No, no.
You have to go to high school.
If I go to high school,
it's meaningless.
You don't study.
I'm studying.
But when I graduate,
I'll go to high school.
It's meaningless to go to high school.
Shut up.
It's meaningful.
I don't work properly. Is it meaningful to go?
Good night.
Sorry for disturbing.
Sit down.
I'm sorry, on your rest day.
I'm glad you're home.
I have red wine.
What do you want to drink?
Water is ok.
What's wrong?
It's been a long time.
No, seriously.
You're not drunk.
I can't drink.
What do you mean?
I'll drink.
Of course.
Let's toast.
Cheers.
It's been a long time.
Did you make me pregnant?
Because there is a baby in me.
Really?
Yes.
Well...
I found out about it
right after we broke up.
I couldn't tell you.
I wanted to meet you
and talk to you.
It's...
the 13th week.
Are you sure
it's my baby?
Yes.
It's the right timing.
Are you...
already dating her?
No.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Why am I here?
Rio.
I'll make sure
not to bother you.
Bother?
I'm sorry.
Bye.
Please see the show's official X for more details.
This is the play I was interested in.
Wait.
You're collecting so much.
That's crazy.
It must have been hard.
No, not at all.
Really?
Do you know about
this kind of play?
When I was little,
my parents took me to a musical.
My parents are divorced.
I'm so jealous.
My mom and dad
are having an affair.
Really?
You're so heavy.
I'm used to it.
I see.
It's not the time to talk about this.
No.
I have to make a decision.
What do you mean?
Do you know
what people in your company say about you?
I don't know.
They say you're the worst.
I don't want to be told
that I cheated on you.
You apologized.
Then why do you repeat the same thing?
If you want to say that,
you have to invest the money.
That's not good.
How many times
do you think you're spending
What do you mean?
I've never been told that.
You've always been like this.
I want to get rid of you for real.
But it costs 500,000 yen.
Ms. Rio?
Yes?
What's wrong?
I was thinking.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go.
Yes.
I've been looking for you.
My name is Yamazoi.
Nice to meet you.
It's been a long time.
This year,
I hope to continue
Shitei High School.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
The students here are very good.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm so tired.
I'm tired.
It's not enough people.
Even though it's a retail market,
it's still here.
I was in trouble.
I'm the commander of the era.
We have to continue
a better company and a better relationship.
That will be the strength of the school.
That's right.
It's still the era of elementary school students.
The school from now on is going to be hard.
Hey,
How about it?
Thank you for your hard work.
What?
No, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I want to go
to the store.
I want to go.
It's okay.
It's the era of elementary school students.
I want to go.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's a very nice store.
I'm glad I couldn't go to the usual store.
That store is
Mr. Goh's branch.
That's right.
Mr. Okuma is in that store.
Can I ask you what you would like to drink?
What would you like to drink?
I'd like to drink jasmine tea.
Mr. Sasaoka, don't you drink?
I've been drinking recently.
I see.
Two beers and
jasmine tea, please.
Thank you.
I
often use this store.
Mr. Kiyoto
is always amazing.
What?
Do you bow your head to people?
No, no, no.
You don't have pride,
but you bow your head to people.
You're like a
symbol of middle management.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
I understand
what you're saying.
I'm really sorry.
Have you really said that?
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I'm kidding.
Thank you for waiting.
It looks delicious.
Eat, eat.
Don't worry.
Eat and drink today.
But if you bow your head
and do well,
I think it's okay.
Our school's
main role is
children.
The main role is
the students.
You two
know each other very well.
Well,
I'm the main role.
Well, well.
I won't let you
take a summer vacation.
That's right.
If Mr. Kiyoto
is great,
I'll follow everything.
Please tell me.
What?
What's wrong?
In the first year,
I thought I could do it.
Well, summer vacation in hell
is too sweet.
Is it that hard?
Well, I understand
But Mr. Okuma
has a good reason
Reason?
The three of them
Do you know the store
Mr. Okuma often goes to?
It's the Alligator store in Urayasu.
The store there
is run by a mother and a daughter.
Oh, Mr. Haru
was the daughter of that store.
You two are
of Mr. Okuma's teacher,
Mr. Wani-buchi.
Oh, Mr. Wani-buchi
is the alligator.
That's why
I went to that store.
I thought it would be better
to live away from school
than to meet everyone.
No, the reason
why you went to that store
is not the reason.
Mr. Wani-buchi
is the teacher
Mr. Okuma
took care of
in the first year
He was a really good teacher.
But a few years later
he was killed
What?
Killed?
That's why
I went to that store.
Mr. Okuma
looks like a very hot person.
No, I didn't know at all.
In my school
Mr. Toyoshima
broke his body
and he lost his mind.
So I asked Mr. Sasaoka
to take care of him.
Yes.
That's why Mr. Okuma
came here
and worked so hard.
He never
let Mr. Wani-buchi
or Mr. Toyoshima
to work
and he had his own way
of working.
At that time
Mr. Wani-buchi passed away
and the students
were really shocked.
They lost their jobs
and the children
who didn't go to school came out.
It was really hard for them.
The 3C students
were also
a little bit
and they were shocked.
Mr. Okuma
I think Mr. Okuma
is doing his best
A teacher
should be respected
and at least
he should do his best
to face
of the students.
What are you talking about?
What?
Seri?
Yes.
You know
I give up on the baby.
What?
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
I think
there are cases
about the teacher.
Yes, but
most of the cases
are deleted.
I looked it up on the internet
but most of the cases
are deleted secretly.
No, it's not like that.
Teachers are such creatures.
They go on summer vacation
and no one will notice
so it's okay.
It's okay.
It's going well.
Here you go.
Is there something wrong?
Actually
I was thinking
It's possible
here, isn't it?
It's possible but
if you come this far
you can't come back.
You have to think about your body
and if you really
give up
you have to go right away.
Are you sure?
Yes.
What are you doing at this hour?
Are you going clubbing again today?
No.
It's been a while.
I'm going to meet someone.
Who?
Someone I respect the most
Teacher Omori?
Yes.
Teacher.
What is
Teacher Omori doing now?
He's making a place for
with NPO.
Teacher Omori.
Even if he's polite
he's a teacher.
I like
teaching
and the kids.
Do you?
Yes, I do.
Rio
Are you okay helping in your rest day?
I like teaching too, It's fun.
Okay.
I don't know what to do with this.
You could start here.
Really, thank you.
You're welcome.
I feel strange bein g with my teacher
having a tea in a fancy place like this.
Really?
I've been here before.
You're a human too.
That's right.
Even teachers are humans.
You were
great.
Great? No...
It's an accident
but
there are a lot of things
I didn't tell you.
Really?
Yes.
What is it?
Well
I had a friend
who was a teacher.
When we were kids?
Much before than Rio was a kid.
We didn't get along.
When we were drinking
we had a fight.
You had a fight?
Yes.
The students
were fighting
and the teachers
were fighting.
It's hard
You'll know
That's right.
I had a fight with a teacher.
Really?
We were fighting.
We used to fight.
You were
a tough guy.
Yes.
It's not just that.
The teacher
said it was bad.
Don't talk.
What?
The teacher
fired him.
Did the teacher go?
No.
He was at the same store.
I'll think about it later.
I think
the teacher came here
and
we had a fight
and we drank.
He was a tough guy.
He paid for it.
What?
He was fired.
Then
the teacher
fired him.
Did the teacher go?
Yes.
It's terrible.
What?
He paid for it.
It's a lie.
It's true.
He was drunk.
I don't know.
Wait.
Did the teacher
get married?
Yes.
Wow.
You changed
your image.
Wait.
Did the teacher
get married?
Yes.
Really?
This is a secret.
This is the first time I talk to you.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
But
I'm sorry.
He was a tough guy.
He was a tough teacher.
I'll tell him.
Don't tell him.
He might buy
my way of drinking.
You've changed.
You were young.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
You're amazing.
You know everything.
I'm fine.
I'm not perfect.
I don't care if I fail.
I'm trying my best.
Teachers are human.
Thank you, teacher
What was that face?
How are you feeling? Are you feeling better?
Yeah, that's right.
But...
You're not asking me anything, are you?
You can tell me if it hurts, right, Rio?
Do you understand now?
That I'm worried about you.
Of course I do.
It's because of you...
...that I'm getting angry.
So, teacher.
Yeah?
Can I come see you again?
You can come anytime.
For a teacher, the greatest joy...
...is when a graduate comes to visit.
Bye, teacher.
Bye.
Hey, Sensei.
Yeah?
The truth is...
...it was all a lie.
I wanted to cheer you up.
We're the same, aren't we?
What?
Hey, Kengo!
Huh?
It's amazing that you came all the way here.
Senpai!
Thank you for your hard work.
What's wrong?
I'm cheering you up.
Here, I brought you honey lemon.
Thank you.
Thank you for the food.
See you.
Your house is this way?
That's right.
We talked about it.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Sensei.
Did you like the honey lemon?
Yeah.
Kengo said so.
What?
I'm so happy.
I think I did a good job.
Hey, senpai.
Sawaiya.
Huh?
What's up?